Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
An Unwanted Guest
Episode 35
I didn’t expect the one left in Goats’ Village to be so awesome.
Needless to say
Each of the students I teach can be independent in their own way.
Dealing with someone who doesn’t play by the rules,
I can only let it solve it.
Go get that guy back. I need him.
What do you want to do?
You win this round
But it won’t necessarily be the next round.
It seems that world is quite far away. I have to hurry up.
Why is there everything here?
I was frightened, but luckily I escaped
Why am I so unlucky?
It’s really boring for us to guard here.
It’s a bit boring here.
But there are monsters in the city now. It would be safer to stay here.
That’s right, but the man we arrested a few days ago
Maybe he brought the monster here
Suddenly I feel like it’s not safe here either
what is this sound
sorry sorry
Are you okay?
Wait, who are you?
How did you get here?
Sorry, I must have come to the wrong place.
I’ll go back right now
What are you doing? Let me go.
Come back with us and be investigated.
I’m really not a monster
Please let me go
I have important things to do
When we meet the prince later, he will judge for himself
I heard you caught a suspicious person in the rift.
Yes Your Highness, that’s him
I was really passing by.
I still want to save
Sparky
Weslie, you are here too
Why are you here?
He actually knows my name.
Wait
You are not the Weslie and Sparky I know
You are ragdolls
What ragdolls?
We are Bulala people
Is the Weslie you are talking about from Green Green Grassland?
Yes, I’m from Green Green Grassland.
No wonder you feel just like Weslie when I touch you.
So, you’re from the same place.
You should hurry and find the two of them, then.
Although we would really like to help,
we’re afraid we can’t assist you for the time being.
Things haven’t been very peaceful around here lately.
Not peaceful?
Reporting, Your Highness! there’s been another incident where a monster injured someone.
What did you say?
Did you get a clear look at what the attacker looked like?
Your Highness, I…
What were you going to say?
What kind of person would be so cruel as to attack an elderly person?
“Elderly person”? I’m only eight years old!
You look like that at just eight years old?
There’s something you don’t know—a monster has appeared here recently.
If it touches you, you lose all your strength,
becoming incredibly weak.
Is this monster really that terrifying?
You’d be better off leaving here soon.
I’ll be going now.
Wait.
You’re an outsider; it’s easy to be mistaken for the monster.
Take this piece of embroidery.
It proves you’ve passed our screening.
That way, the soldiers along the way won’t give you any trouble.
Alright. Then I’m off to save my friend.
I’m too hungry to walk.
Young man, are you hungry?
Yes. Do you have anything good to eat?
Welcome to my restaurant.
Let’s go inside.
Here you go—scallion oil noodles.
Take your time eating.
Then I won’t stand on ceremony.
All right.
Owner, another bowl, please.
Coming right up.
Owner, another bowl—without scallions.
Owner, another bowl, please.
Please, stop eating. It’s not good for your health.
But we aren’t full yet.
Not full yet?
But I’ve run out of ingredients.
I guess that’s all for today, then.
I suppose we’ll have to settle for being eighty percent full today.
It’s been a long time since I’ve eaten with such gusto.
I never expected to meet a kindred spirit here.
Have you forgotten? We’ve met before—in the desert.
So, that was you.
But how did a Bulala person end up in the Blue Planet world?
I wanted to go traveling back then,
but I accidentally stumbled into that rift.
I passed through it and visited many places, seeing all sorts of different scenery.
Do you know this place, then?
Never mind, you probably wouldn’t know it.
I do know it; I’ve been there.
Really? Could you take me there?
Of course. Having someone to travel and dine with
is a wonderful thing.
Then let’s set off together.
My name is Paddi. What about you?
You can just call me Green.
I’m sorry, Your Highness.
We’ve searched everywhere,
but still haven’t found the monster.
Where on earth could it be hiding?
Searching blindly all over the place is useless.
We need to get the answer from the victim.
I was attacked while traveling alone to the small town to visit my grandmother.
I was attacked while eating an apple alone.
I was attacked while going to see the princess alone.
It seems like there’s nothing in common.
No, they were all attacked while alone.
Issue my order: search the entire city,
and no one is allowed to travel alone.
Yes.
Come to think of it, someone was moving around alone…
Paddi.
They’re so busy; they’ve probably found the monster by now.
How come you aren’t afraid of the monster?
I am afraid, but I have you with me, don’t I?
Then you’ve really come to the right person—I’m amazing at this.
Green, why do you look so pale?
Did something you ate upset your stomach?
Are you okay?
I’m fine, just a little hungry.
Look over there.
Finally, I’ve found a new body.
This body fills me with energy; it’s a perfect match for me.
I’ll never need to switch bodies to maintain my energy again.
To think the perfect body I’ve been searching for was actually him.
I think I zoned out for a moment there. Are you okay?
I’m…I’m fine.
I get dizzy easily if I don’t eat enough.
Here, take this.
The restaurant owner gave it to us earlier; go ahead and eat.
Okay, thanks.
I didn’t expect his mental strength to be stronger than an ordinary person’s.
It looks like I’ll have to take over his body while he’s unconscious.
I saw through your tricks a long time ago.
D-did you find me out?
I knew all along. Come out now!
Since you’ve found me out, I have no choice but to…
Watch out!
This monster has been stalking us for a long time.
So, you weren’t talking to me.
Did it get away?
Darn it, what is the deal with this Paper Beast?
Green, can you hear me?
Peach?
Green, we need you here. Come back fast.
I…I can’t go back just yet.
I’m so close to getting a perfect body.
Don’t you dare hurt him.
The chance to take over the body is here.
Thank goodness I made it in time.
Seize that monster!
Yes.
Paddi, wake up.
Oh, it’s you guys. What brings you here?
We were analyzing the case and were worried you might be in danger.
We didn’t expect to arrive just as you were being attacked.
I see. Thank you.
How did you catch him?
We suspect he is that monster.
What? He’s the monster?
It’s too dangerous here.
I’d better leave right away.
Thanks, everyone. Goodbye.
How did he walk away so fast?
Oh well, let’s go too.
To be continued